Jordan Nash

Software Developer

I am a professional, object orientated, C# software developer with 3 years experience. Graduated with a Diploma of Software Development in 2016 and have actively been creating various projects on GitHub including Pitcher. Pitcher is a web bug tracker created with agile sprints, an SRS and a third-party login service to reduce development workload. I am using the app currently to log my own errors. Please check portfolio for project demo image. Passionate about software development. Looking to join a development team in Brisbane.



Logan

- inash51@live.com

 inash51@live.com
- Brisbane, Australia
- in linkedin.com/in/jordan-nash-87b042173

- Available on recruiter's request
- layersofabstraction.github.io/#
- github.com/LayersOfAbstraction

SKILLS



EDUCATION

Diploma of Software Development Tafe

01/2015 - 06/2016 Logan

Certificate 3 Individual Support TAFE

01/2017 - 07/2017

WORK EXPERIENCE

Support Worker

Way Future Support Services

08/2020 - Present

Achievements/Tasks

- Connected client to group activities outside his home
- Built rapport with client
- Got companion card so a client can attend more venues and enjoy more enrichment

Support Worker

Community Support Pty Ltd

08/2020 - 10/2020

Achievements/Tasks

- Successfully encouraged client to go outside home
- Successfully encouraged client to go to school many times
- Made client feel safe

Support WorkerUniting Care Queensland

Achievements/Tasks

- Guided client around outdoor areas
- Engaged client to pass the time during train trips
- Kept client safe

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Pitcher - Bug logger software

- Implement 3rd party login service Auth0 rather than creating login system from scratch
- Successfully Logged bugs found in the software as problem tickets in the backend project database
- Used ASP.NET MVC with Entity Framework to build project
- Transformed solved bug logs into technical HOW-TO blogs in my portfolio

FTDC File Time Date Converter

 Created API to auto rename multiple selected files across windows file system to filename specified by user

Portfolio

- Created beautiful layout in responsive Media Query Design
- Attached blogging engine written in Jekyll Static Site Generator to easily create highly detailed technical HOW-TO blogs

Undercover multipurpose recreation area

- Published video https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zqh_gvzzd1k
- Got on Front page of the Southern Star about idea implementation https://i.imgur.com/XoD0viV.jpg article content here https://tinyurl.com/m5v2herk
- Got petition published on Brisbane Council website with help from Ben Strickland https://tinyurl.com/b7w3z8ne and made brochure idea https://tinyurl.com/3fvzucu3

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Volunteer Zi Zai Dong Zen

08/2017 - 07/2020

Tasks/Achievements

• Did Qi Gong on people with illnesses learned from master

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freestyle slalom skating coach Self Employed

10/2018 - 06/2021

Achievements/Tasks

- Taught children and adults basic skate skills and advanced freestyle slalom skills
- Made detailed and easy to understand practice plans so my clients know exactly what to do and how to practice basic tricks
- Improved client's self-esteem and confidence

Assistant cook

MacDonald's and Hungry Jacks

06/2010 - 01/2013

Achievements/Tasks

- Kept team stocked up on essential items from outdoor freezer
- Put fillet burgers together quickly
- Emptied containers quickly for team to refill

Action Recliner assembly worker Acme Furniture Australia Pty Ltd

04/2007 - 01/2010

Achievements/Tasks

- Swiftly assembled heavy duty parts into recliners
- Stacked heavy recliners into pile to be used for furniture
- Did this somewhat dangerous work without injury

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Volunteer support workerVarious support worker companies

08/2017 - 07/2020

Tasks/Achievements

- Volunteering as a support worker with several companies
- Exposed to violent and confrontational clients
- Simplified tasks for clients to meet their goals

Strawberry Sundae Stalls helperPrince Charles Hospital Foundation

06/2017 - 06/2017

I was an all-rounder doing the ice cream scooping, mashing the strawberries, serving the customers ice cream.